# **Shreekant Kembhavi**

DevOps Specialist

#313, East Lane, Wembley, London United Kingdom HA0 3LG | +44 7488 508 999 | shreekant.pk@gmail.com

#### **SUMMARY**

Dedicated to optimization, experienced DevOps Engineer understands the melding of operations and development to quickly deliver code to customers. Has experience with the Cloud and monitoring processes as well as DevOps development in Windows Mac and Linux systems. Brings a master's degree in Information Technology and experience working as a DevOps Engineer since shortly after the concept was introduced.

# **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Kubernetes, Dynatrace, Python, Azure DevOps, Jenkins, Cloud Foundry, Azure Cloud, GIT, Openstack, CentOs, Docker, Jira, Postman

## **CORE QUALIFICATION**

- Over 5 years of work experience as DevOps Engineer coupling with 7 years of computer science education.
- Familiar with Azure, Cloud Foundry and OpenStack.
- Monitoring using tools like Dynatrace.
- Usage of Kubernetes, Docker, git, Jira and other DevOps tools.
- Strong use of Interpreted Languages including Python.
- Good use of database including MySql.
- Extremely knowledgeable about CI/CD using Jenkins.
- Facility with development methodologies including Agile.
- Documentation using confluence, wiki and SAP Jam.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Tech Architecture Delivery Specialist | (July 2019 – present)

# Accenture, London, United Kingdom

- Involved in maintaining infrastructure including Kubernetes on Azure Cloud. Maintaining repositories and release of product using Azure DevOps.
- Setting up and Integrating Airflow on Azure to schedule containers using Python.
- Setting up alerting and monitoring on Azure.
- Involved in creating pipelines for CI/CD.

DevOps Engineer | (July 2017 - July 2019) SAP Labs, Bangalore, India

- Onboarding customers on SAP Leonardo IoT Platform on Cloud foundry.
- Minimizing the tasks using REST API using postman.
- Configured Dynatrace for monitoring IoT Applications

#### **EDUCATION**

Masters in Information
Technology – 2:1 ( Dec 2012)
The University of Nottingham,
United Kingdom

Bachelor of Engineering in Information Science and Engineering – First Class (2012) B.N.M. Institute of Technology, Bangalore, India

Diploma in Information Science and Technology – First Class (2006) N.V. Polytechnic, Gulbarga, India

- and infrastructure including HANA database.
- Migrated the Jenkins system that was launching from docker on to Kubernetes.
- Integrated Jenkins as admin for CI/CD.

Release Engineer | (Nov 2016 - July 2017) Oracle, Bangalore, India

- Release development for Oracle Fusion HCM cloud.
- Involved in applying weekly and monthly patch bundles in the pods.
- Used Bugzilla for tracking bugs.

Software Engineer | (June 2014 - Nov 2016)
Cisco, Bangalore, India
Vendors: Randstad India Limited and Volen softwares

- Develop and maintain CI/CD system that works on cloud and virtualization.
- Using Openstack as the cloud.
- Develop and configure a log file server using ELK stack and monitoring system using Shinken.
- Automating apps deployment and infrastructure deployment using ansible.
- Using Docker for full stack building.
- Used Rally for working in Agile, Jenkins for CI/CD, Mantis for tracking bugs.